# 新疆·乌鲁木齐
Xinjiang Urumqi
# 现在我们所在的位置是大巴扎步行街
Where we are now is the grand bazaar promenade
# 走啦 今天我们要去吃吃喝喝
Let's go. Today we will eat and drink
(timeline missing)
# 馕
Naan
# 大叔 那个是刷的什么东西
What did you brush?
# 鸡蛋
Egg
# 这边是刷的鸡蛋
oh It was brushed in egg
# 这多少钱一个
How much is it?
# 5块钱
5 yuan
# 拿一个
Take one
# 这几块的 5块
How much is it? 5 yuan
# 支付宝也可以是吧
Alipay is allowed,right?
# 可以
okay
# 他是后面擀馕 然后
He rolled the naan in the back
# 把馕放在一个小墩子上
then put naan on a small ( )
# 把馕放进馕坑里
Put naan in the naan oven
# 看
Look
# 馕坑是特别的高
The naan oven is so tall
# 随着（馕贴在壁上的声音）一声
With the sound of KUNG (naan was stuck on the oven)
# 馕就被贴在里面了
Naan was stuck in it
# 馕做好后 要用两个小钩子
When the naan is done
# 把它从里面捞出来
remove it with two small hooks
# 这到底要怎么下口
Ah How should I eat it?
# 像一个脸盘这么大
As big as a face
# 这个馕就是外面有点脆
This naan is just a little crispy on the outside
# 但是里面还是有稍微松软的口感的
But there's a little bit of softness in it
# 这么吃是带点咸味的
It tastes a little salty
# 我觉得它可能少一些烤肉
I think it might need some barbecue
# 把它卷进去来吃
to roll it in
# 这边只有红柳烤肉吗
Is there only tamarisk meat here
(timeline missing)
# 还有普通烤肉
It still has regular roast meat
# 普通的烤肉是哪一种
What's a regular roast?
(timeline missing)
# 有没有烤好的让我看一看
Let me have a look
# 这种是普通的 是吧
Is this regular one,right?
(timeline missing)
# 这是红柳
This is tamarisk meat
# 那你给我拿上四个红柳的
Then you bring me four tamarisks ones
# 它那个肉是一样的吗
( )
# 对 肉是一样的 只不过说签子不一样
Yes meat is the same just the prods are different
# 签子烤出来就香一点 用那个红柳枝串的
( )
# 红柳枝子烤串肉也多一点
# 4个
four
# 刚才说这个馕缺烤肉嘛
I just said this naan lacks roast meat
# 然后我们就是
And then we had
# 5块钱的馕 配了30块钱的红柳烤肉
5 yuan naan with 30 yuan tamarind
# 嘿
Hey
# 它好像不能够（被撸下来）
he can't seem to be ( )
# 不行 不行 不行
no no no
# 刚才那个镜头是失败的
That scene was a failure
# 因为红柳烤肉
Because of the roast beef
# 肉感觉是直接粘在签子上的
The meat feels directly attached to the prod
# 没办法撸下来
It can't be( )
# 我们只能是吃着烤肉 配着馕
We can only eat barbecue with naan
# 一个顶三个
( )
# 吃完三个烤肉 感觉已经很饱了
Eat three kebabs I feel very full
# 现在快八点了 但是天还没有黑的意思
It's almost eight o 'clock but it's not dark yet
# 我们再继续逛一逛吧
Let's go on hanging
# 那边有跳舞的 我们要去看一看
There are dancers over there and we're going to have a look
# 马路的对面主要是卖东西吃的
The main street across the street is selling food
# 这一边就是小礼品 工艺品比较多一些
Here has more arts crafts and souvenir
# 这边有个馕主题馆 我们要进去逛一下
There's a nan-themed pavilion here. We're going in
# 什么是馕 说的天花乱坠 倒不如一看究竟
What's naan?( )
# 哇
wow
# 在文化馆里 摆放着几十种的馕
Dozens of varieties of naan are displayed in the cultural hall
# 它们的颜色 大小 厚薄 形状各不相同
()
# 常见的像 油馕 肉馕 窝窝馕 芝麻馕 等等
Such as Younaan Meatnaan Wowonaan sesamenaan
# 走这么一圈下来 可能记住的也没几个
Walk down such a circle may remember a few
# 这个时候 尝 应该是加深记忆的一个好方法
So taste should be a good way to deepen your memory
# 免费和花钱买
()
# 这边到底有多少人 在等一个馕呢
How many people here are waiting for a naan
# 关 注
# 雪 鱼 探 店
(Subscribe)